e4me.ae 2018-08-13

# Etisalat UAE | Privacy Policy

### YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal information is any information that is specific to a particular customer.  
We may collect your personal information such as:  
\- Your name, gender, date of birth, identity document number  
\- Your delivery and/or your billing addresses, telephone number, fax number, email address  
\- Your banking information, debit or credit card details  
\- Information on products and services purchased by you  
\- Your preferences for particular products and services  
\- Your demographic information, education level, occupation, household income, interests and activities  
\- The channel you chose to purchase our products or services  
\- How you use our products and services, which may include your traffic data and the date, time, duration and cost of your communications and the types of websites that you visit, your spend, your device details, your phone usage, your purchasing habits, your location, your searching and browsing history on our websites  
\- Your amount of data usage, roaming information, internet protocol (IP) address which we collect when you visit our websites and your device details, the date and time of your visit to our websites, the type and version of browser used, the operating system and platform and the URL of any websites which you used to access our websites  
\- Your communications with us  
\- Your account information such as your billing history, the services you use and anything else relating to your account  
\- Any information necessary to make a credit check with credit reporting agencies  
\- Any other information we need to provide a particular service  
If you give us personal information about another person that we have requested in relation to the provision of a service, you are responsible for ensuring that they know and agree to us keeping records about them and that we will process their personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### SHARING AND DISCLOSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Your personal information may be shared with, or transferred to, our subsidiaries and affiliated companies and trusted third parties (including agents, subcontractors and suppliers who are integral to providing some of our services). In purchasing or subscribing to a product or service, you agree that we may share your personal information in such manner. However, you always have the option to withdraw your consent by contacting the etisalat Contact Centre.  
We may also disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation or to protect the rights, property, or safety of etisalat, our customers or others. We may share your personal information with reputable credit reporting agencies for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.  
We may share your personal information for emergency services, including your approximate location.  
We may be required to disclose your personal information or legally intercept the services to comply with the laws of the UAE or the express instructions of a competent authority (such as the Telecommunications Regulatory Authority) or where it is deemed necessary in the interests of public or national security.  
In addition, we may share aggregated and/or anonymized (non-personally identifiable) information, derived from your personal information, publicly and with our partners such as publishers, advertisers, website owners etc. 

Breakpoint: xs ( 375px ), Viewport width: 

Breakpoint: ms ( 375px ), Viewport width: 

Breakpoint: sm ( 768px ), Viewport width: 

Breakpoint: md ( 992px ), Viewport width: 

Breakpoint: lg ( 1440px ), Viewport width: 

Breakpoint: xl ( 1600px ), Viewport width:
